{"data":[{"question":"Last autumn Yvonne took a course on ___.","a":"how aprons be made","b":"how to make aprons","c":"how aprons to be made","d":"how to be made aprons","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Some verbs: ask, decide, explain, forget, know, show, tell, understand, can be followed by a question word such as where\/ how\/ what\/ who\/ when or whether + To Verb ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The light in your room is still on, Alice. \"Oh, I forgot to ___\"","a":"turn it off","b":"turning it off","c":"having turned it off","d":"turned it off","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Forget + V_ing: Forget something which have already happened\/done \n- Forget+ To Verb: Forget To do something ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"There are so many kinds of digital cameras on sale that I can't make up my mind _________ to buy.","a":"which","b":"what","c":"where","d":"how","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Which: We use which when the number of choices is limited ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Little Oscar should love ___ to the zoo this afternoon.","a":"to take","b":"to be taken","c":"taking","d":"being taken","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Love + to Verb \n- Passive voice: Love + to be past p\u1ea3ticiple","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"That 14-year-old boy can hardly be imagined ___ across the Atlantic Ocean in six days.","a":"to sail","b":"sail","c":"to have sailed","d":"sailing","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Imagine + Verb_ing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I would appreciate ___ back today.","a":"you call","b":"you to call","c":"you're calling","d":"you calling","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Appreciate sbd doing somthing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I usually go to school by bus \"Why not ___ by bicycle for a change?\"","a":"trying to go","b":"to try going","c":"try going","d":"to try and go","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Try + To Verb: attempt to do\/make an effort to do \n- Try + Verb_ing: do something as an experiment or test","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"You were brave and bold to raise objections to the boss's face at the meeting. \"Well, now I regret ___ that.\"","a":"to be doing","b":"to do","c":"having done","d":"to have done","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Regret+To Verb: Feel regret for something you are going to do \n- Regret + Verb-ing: Feel regret for something already happened","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you remember ___ me at a lawn party in this summer vacation?","a":"to meet","b":"meet","c":"met","d":"meeting","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Remember+ V_ing: Remember something which have already happened\/done \n- Remember+ To Verb: Remember to do something (need to be done)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The crowd couldn't help ___ the foolish emperor in the procession.","a":"to laugh at","b":"laugh at","c":"laughing on","d":"laughing at","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Couldn't help + Verb_ing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}